# JASON SILVIA

Creative Content Developer

# **EDUCATION**

New England Institute of Technology East Greenwich, RI 2008 — 2011 Bachelor of Science - IT Networking

Full Sail University Winter Park, FL 2004 — 2005 Associate of Arts - Recording Arts

## **SKILLS**

- Content Creation & Management
- Project Management
- Audio Engineering
- Music & Podcast Production
- Copywriting
- Image & Video Editing
- Graphic Design
- Technical Solution Design and Consulting

- 401-451-6186
- ✓ JGSilvia11@gmail.com
- jasonsilvia.com | linkedin.com/in/jasonsilvia
- Providence, RI

# **SUMMARY**

Multi-disciplined creative professional with 10 years experience, and a passion for both tech and the arts. Seeking to utilize my skills and experience in content consulting & creation, project management, marketing, and copywriting in the fields of content creation and production.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Freelance**

Dec 2020 - Present Providence, RI

#### **Copywriter and Content Producer**

 Providing creative content consulting, content production, and audio/video media services to businesses.

#### Freelance

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022 San Francisco, CA

# **Marketing Content Developer**

- Developed marketing content and owned production process end to end
- Duties included storyboarding, copywriting, voiceovers, video editing, image editing, music production

# **Dell Technologies**

Nov 2019 - Dec 2020 Hopkinton, MA

# **Specialty Content Consultant**

- Analyzed, curated, and created training content for unstructured data and data protection orgs
- Advised business leadership on the creation of new/updated presales training content

#### **Dell Technologies**

Jun 2017 - Nov 2019 Hopkinton, MA

#### **Solutions Architect**

- Designed and presented technology solutions for sales campaigns
- Acted as technical expert for presales activities
- Created and presented training materials and product demos

#### **Dell Technologies**

Mar 2015 - Jun 2017 Hopkinton, MA

# **Technical Service Engineer**

• Provided technical support expertise for all flash storage array products

#### **Schneider Electric**

Jun 2012 - Dec 2013 West Kingston, RI

### **Email Retention Marketing Specialist**

 Design, production, and management of email marketing campaigns for North America and Global orgs